You make me dance, yeah you do
You got my heart beatin' rhythms when you move
Don't need no plans, feeling loose
Like there's a rainbow of magic next to you
When it's good, when it's bad, yeah, you got me
Not alone in this town 'cause you make me feel
Anytime that I call, you'll be ready
Anytime, anytime
And when I turn around, I see you there
You got a way to make a problem disappear
Up to the clouds, I'm spinning 'round
And now you know why
'Cause no one in this world can make me feel loved
In the way that you do now
No, no one in this world can make me come down
When I'm in this so good, good mood now
Woo-hoo (ooh)
Good mood
Hop in my ride, don't you know, oh?
We got the sun always shinning wherever we go
Don't need no map, we just roll
Let the vibe give direction, take control
When it's good, when it's bad, yeah, you got me
Not alone in this town 'cause you make me feel
Anytime that I call, you'll be ready
Anytime, anytime
And when I turn around, I see you there
You got a way to make a problem disappear
Up to the clouds, I'm spinning 'round
And now you know why
'Cause no one in this world can make me feel loved
In the way that you do now
No, no one in this world can make me come down
When I'm in this so good, good mood now
Woo-hoo (yeah, ooh)
Good mood
Oh-oh
Woo-hoo
You make me feel good (oh)
Good mood
Yeah, oh
You make me in a good mood
Woo-hoo
Yeah-yeah
Hey
Oh-oh-oh
You make me feel good (woo-hoo)
Woo-hoo, ooh
You make me feel good
Woo-hoo
Good mood
You make me
Woo-hoo
Woo
Good mood